[Music]
funeral homes was established to provide
modern state-of-the-art and
comprehensive funeral services
if a family lost a loved one everything
became a do-it-yourself affair but last
year if you know homes was established
so that everything that has to do with
the funeral from the time a person dies
until they're buried
can all be done
and made available in one place and at
all time to emphasize the importance of
treating
the body of the deceased
with the utmost respect and dignity
largely funeral homes provides any and
all services
that have to do
with funerals that should be funeral
homes will recover the body from
wherever the death occurred and bomb the
body using the most modern techniques we
will keep the body or store the body in
our state-of-the-art
refrigeration system for as long as the
family desires
nearer the time of the funeral we will
prepare and dress the body up for the
funeral we provide transportation namely
ambulances and hershey's
to convey the body from one place to the
other
as the family may wish
we also provide on our premises the
services of an interdenominational
chapel
where
services can be conducted
we also have the only modern crematory
in ghana at the moment which services
not only ghana but also cote d'ivoire we
also have
a cemetery
one of the only two
privately managed cemeteries in accra at
the moment
all it takes literally is one telephone
call and perhaps two visits to our
premises for everything to do with the
funeral to be arranged for you
[Music]
there are several funeral plans on the
market
most of them
are based
on the premise that when the insured
person passes away
the insurance company will pay an agreed
sum of money to the bereaved family
often enough
the sum
paid to the family may not be sufficient
to cover
the basic needs
the family requires
that is where
the
prudential dignity plan comes into its
own and is significantly different
because
what the prudential dignity plan
ensures
are the services
that will be required
so that it does not matter
whether five years or ten years after
the insurance was taken
those services
will be provided
regardless of the fact that the costs
may have gone up once you are insured
your services are covered it doesn't
matter how long before the death or case
dignity failed plan from prudential life
insurance in partnership with la chibi
funeral homes is providing families with
over a decade of experience and peace of
mind when it comes to saying goodbye to
your loved ones
to find out more or to sign up to the
dignity farewell plan contact us today
[Music]